ngadventure.typepad.com 2010-12-30

# National Geographic Privacy Policy Highlights

### What This Statement Covers

This statement applies to www.nationalgeographic.com, the Web site of the National Geographic Society. For more information, please read our complete Privacy Policy. To review additional measures we take in relation to children's privacy, please view our[ Kids Privacy Policy](http://www.nationalgeographic.com/kids/privacy.html). 

* * *

### Your Personal Information

• In general, you can visit us on the Internet without telling us who you are or giving us personal information. There are times we may ask you to provide personal information, for example, to process an order, provide a subscription, or participate in a contest.

• We may supplement this information with information obtained from other National Geographic services and other organizations.

• We keep track of your interactions with our sites and our services to offer a more personalized experience. 

Additional Details »

### Uses of Information

• We use the information we collect to provide the services you request. Our services may include the display of personalized content and advertising.

• We use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by National Geographic, our affiliates, and our licensees.

• We may share information about you with selected other organizations for offers of their products and services.

• We do not share your e-mail address with other organizations for offers of their products and services unless you allow us to do so.

Additional Details »

* * *

### Your Privacy Choices

• You may direct us not to send you promotional materials from National Geographic, our affiliates, and our licensees.

• You may direct us not to share your information with selected other organizations for offers of their products and services.

Additional Details »

### Contact Us

Questions about this statement or National Geographic's privacy policy may be sent to:

National Geographic Society  
Attn: Marketing Services - Privacy  
1145 17th Street NW  
Washington, DC 20036-4688

You may also contact us by telephone at:  
**Toll-Free—U.S. and Canada only:**  
800 NGS LINE (800 647 5463) or 800 548 9797 (TDD)  
**Outside the U.S. and Canada:**  
+1 813 979 6845
